anniescostumes.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy

**Credit Card Security**

Our secure shopping cart is provided by Magento Commerce. Our secure credit card processing is provided by Transfirst. Your credit card information is SSL encrypted and kept secure behind firewalls and the latest technology. We are proud to offer the highest level of credit card privacy and security.

**COOKIES**

**Metamorphic eCommerce, Inc.** web sites use an independent company for tracking. Our tracking software uses cookies so that we can keep track of our advertising campaigns and site efficiency. These cookies are known as your "Unique Visitor Cookie", a Small piece of data, identifying you only by random number (e.g. #12345). No personal information can be identified about the user through cookies. This numerical data is sent to the user's browser from a Web server and then stored onto the user's computer hard drive. Through modification of browser preferences, a user can elect to accept all cookies, receive notification when a cookie is set or decline all cookies. The purpose of this type of tracking is that the figures we obtain can be used to make sure that we are providing the best online user experience for our visitors and to monitor different advertising campaigns for effectiveness, ultimately to keep our costs down, which, in turn, keeps our retail prices as low as possible. We pass on our savings to our customers in the form of the low retail pricing.

**Use of Data Collected**

We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners or affiliates. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data for marketing and promotional purposes. By using this site, you agree that you may be contacted by third party offers.

**Disclosure**

From time to time, we work with other companies and their agents to perform operational services, such as website design, payment processing, database management and to implement customer surveys to measure satisfaction and to identify new needs. We also provide postal addresses to our shipping companies for delivery purposes. In the course of providing such services, these companies may have contact with your personally identifiable information. By contractual agreement, these companies are required to comply with this Policy. Metamorphic eCommerce, Inc. is not liable for any damages that may result from misuse of your personal information by these companies.

**Testimonials & Photos**

From time to time, we publish testimonials & photographs on our site. By submitting photos, testimonials to us either through any of our websites, blog or social media outlets, such as Facebook, or to our customer service department you are providing royalty-free, unlimited consent to Metamorphic eCommerce, Inc. to modify and publish the content you have submitted.

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Metamorphic eCommerce, Inc. Please be aware that Metamorphic eCommerce, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by our network of websites, Metamorphic eCommerce, Inc.

**Business Transfers**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that Metamorphic eCommerce, Inc. or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

**How do I opt-out from receiving email communications?**

In all emails we send there is an opt-out link. If you click the opt-out link, you will be opted-out from the all promotional emails. However if you place an order with us, and provide the email address, you would only receive emails regarding that specific order, its processing, and shipment. Opt Out of Promotional Emails Link

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

Our business is constantly changing. Over time, our Privacy Notice and Conditions of Use will change as well. Unless otherwise stated, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information and/or email practices regarding information that we have about you and your account. We value the trust you place in us when you shop with us. If we change this privacy statement in ways that affect the personally identifying information we have collected through our sites, we will post those changes in this space and advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes.

**SECURE SHOPPING CART PROVIDED BY MAGENTO COMMERCE. SECURE CREDIT CARD GATEWAY AND CREDIT CARD SERVICES PROVIDED BY PayPal. SSL SECURITY CERTIFIED BY GODADDY.**

Metamorphic eCommerce, Inc. is a family owned and operated company!
